[{"answer": "I should be asking you.", "docId": "110815pmt", "aSentId": 7, "question": "Why is that?", "qSentId": 6}, {"answer": "Well, she does.", "docId": "110815pmt", "aSentId": 33, "question": "What is your view?", "qSentId": 32}, {"answer": "I don't think people are rushing up to you on the streets of America saying legalize heroin.", "docId": "110815pmt", "aSentId": 146, "question": "Yes?", "qSentId": 145}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110815pmt", "aSentId": 148, "question": "That's common sense, are they?", "qSentId": 147}, {"answer": "I think you're mixed up.", "docId": "110815pmt", "aSentId": 167, "question": "That's not supporting choice, it is?", "qSentId": 166}, {"answer": "I can't hammer nails for the rest of my life.", "docId": "110815pmt", "aSentId": 223, "question": "What would you hope to gain from this?", "qSentId": 222}, {"answer": "You know, I don't think that there's a lot to be gained from the might-have-beens, to the would-have-beens, to the could-have- beens of life.", "docId": "110815pmt", "aSentId": 234, "question": "When you have seen what's happened to America, and you have seen the emergence of the Tea Party as a proper formidable political force, do you feel a slight twinge of regret that you're not at the forefront of this?", "qSentId": 233}, {"answer": "I would say I absolutely believe in the notion of tax reform.", "docId": "110815pmt", "aSentId": 256, "question": "But do you agree then with Warren Buffett when he said today that the tax system has to be reformed to hammer people like him more, the super rich who are paying a disproportionate amount of tax and their total tax rates compared to the guy on the street?", "qSentId": 255}, {"answer": "I think that the primary system will winnow that out.", "docId": "110815pmt", "aSentId": 274, "question": "Who do you think fundamentally has what it takes in the overall package to seriously challenge Barack Obama?", "qSentId": 273}, {"answer": "ANFORD: Well, you know, you're trying to get me to pick a horse and I don't want to do that.", "docId": "110815pmt", "aSentId": 278, "question": "What would you say?", "qSentId": 277}, {"answer": "Well, I think that there's talk of that still happening.", "docId": "110815pmt", "aSentId": 294, "question": "Do you think he is persuadable as we get through the next few months and we're heading towards the first proper primary, could you see him rallying to the cause of the party if no one has emerged by then that people don't think could beat Obama?", "qSentId": 293}, {"answer": "Absolutely, yes.", "docId": "110815pmt", "aSentId": 300, "question": "Presumably, you would lean more towards a Tea Party nominee than you would towards one of the more moderate type like a Romney?", "qSentId": 299}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110815pmt", "aSentId": 303, "question": "Is she the obvious person now beginning to capture enough of the public's imagination to potentially be that person?", "qSentId": 302}, {"answer": "I'm not going to pick a horse.", "docId": "110815pmt", "aSentId": 312, "question": "But of those names, of the three, you know, which one if you had to put one in the race tomorrow?", "qSentId": 311}, {"answer": "It's humbling.", "docId": "110815pmt", "aSentId": 343, "question": "How does that feel?", "qSentId": 342}, {"answer": "Well, I think that -- I mean, anybody who has been married doesn't start at the beginning thinking boy, I hope I some day get divorced.", "docId": "110815pmt", "aSentId": 360, "question": "Given that, do you feel great regret, or is that the wrong emotion to put to you?", "qSentId": 359}, {"answer": "I think learned a lot.", "docId": "110815pmt", "aSentId": 379, "question": "What do you think you have learned about yourself?", "qSentId": 378}, {"answer": "They're incredible.", "docId": "110815pmt", "aSentId": 388, "question": "How has the public been with you?", "qSentId": 387}, {"answer": "It was fabulous.", "docId": "110815pmt", "aSentId": 403, "question": "How did that make you feel?", "qSentId": 402}, {"answer": "A whole host of things, none of which are particularly productive in terms of my boys, who might be watching this show.", "docId": "110815pmt", "aSentId": 421, "question": "What would you do differently?", "qSentId": 420}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110815pmt", "aSentId": 424, "question": "Would anything have really made much difference?", "qSentId": 423}, {"answer": "I would hope so.", "docId": "110815pmt", "aSentId": 454, "question": "Having got it wrong in your marriage, do you feel like you have learned enough from that whole experience, and the bruising exposure and scandal to get it right now?", "qSentId": 453}, {"answer": "Oh, yeah.", "docId": "110815pmt", "aSentId": 456, "question": "Are you happier in yourself now, do you think?", "qSentId": 455}, {"answer": "Fabulous.", "docId": "110815pmt", "aSentId": 476, "question": "How would you describe the experience?", "qSentId": 475}, {"answer": "I think that there is a tremendous value to the valleys of life, that the football team that loses on Friday night probably thinks a whole lot more of what they might get right or what they might do differently than the team that won.", "docId": "110815pmt", "aSentId": 493, "question": "What are you thinking when you're there?", "qSentId": 492}, {"answer": "They say so.", "docId": "110815pmt", "aSentId": 507, "question": "Have you, in an odd way, had more time now to develop a better relationship with your sons than you may have done if you continued in the ever more punishing political world?", "qSentId": 506}, {"answer": "I've redeveloped a really neat relationship with my sister.", "docId": "110815pmt", "aSentId": 520, "question": "Who of your family have been the real rocks of support outside of your sons?", "qSentId": 519}, {"answer": "I mean, the obvious in terms of I'm disappointed and here is why.", "docId": "110815pmt", "aSentId": 531, "question": "What did she say to you?", "qSentId": 530}, {"answer": "Important one.", "docId": "110815pmt", "aSentId": 534, "question": "Which is a pretty powerful endorsement to have, isn't it?", "qSentId": 533}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110815pmt", "aSentId": 550, "question": "You must be tempted, aren't you, to have another go at this?", "qSentId": 549}, {"answer": "I don't think it's a question of the tax system.", "docId": "110815pmt", "aSentId": 565, "question": "If you had the power, what is the one thing you would do to dramatically reform the tax system, which would make a real difference in reducing America's debt?", "qSentId": 564}, {"answer": "Well, yes.", "docId": "110815pmt", "aSentId": 569, "question": "It can't just be cutting spending, can it?", "qSentId": 568}, {"answer": "Well, I would argue no.", "docId": "110815pmt", "aSentId": 571, "question": "At some stage, you have to bring in more revenues as well, don't you?", "qSentId": 570}, {"answer": "It's true.", "docId": "110815pmt", "aSentId": 601, "question": "How did you feel about that?", "qSentId": 600}, {"answer": "We'll see.", "docId": "110815pmt", "aSentId": 605, "question": "Do you have any plans to remarry?", "qSentId": 604}, {"answer": "Nor is it an answer.", "docId": "110815pmt", "aSentId": 607, "question": "That's not a denial, Mr. Governor?", "qSentId": 606}, {"answer": "I think so.", "docId": "110815pmt", "aSentId": 611, "question": "Would it be a nice ending to the saga for you?", "qSentId": 610}, {"answer": "No, you're going into -- again that personal sphere that out of respect for my boys --", "docId": "110815pmt", "aSentId": 614, "question": "You have, haven't you?", "qSentId": 613}]